A Guide to the Arts, Education and Americans Panel records FA082
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Norris Houghton Files, 1958-1979; 4; 2.4 Cubic Feet
  Subseries A - Subject Files
  Subseries B - Chronological Files
  - Subject Files, A
    This subseries includes both American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) and National Council for the Arts in Education (NCAIE) materials.
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) - Awards and Recognitions, 1973-1975 (Box 35, Folder 260)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) - Basic Papers, 1973-1974 (Box 35, Folder 261)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) - Conferences, 1975, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 262)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) - Council, 1972-1977 (Box 35, Folder 263)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) - Council, 1972-1977 (Box 35, Folder 264)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) - Council, 1972-1977 (Box 35, Folder 265)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) - Council, 1972-1977 (Box 35, Folder 266)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) - Dissemination and Publication, 1976-1977 (Box 36, Folder 267)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) - Grants, 1972, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 268)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) Panel, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 269)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) Panel, 1974-1975 (Box 36, Folder 270)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) Panel - Bibliographical Material, 1975 (Box 36, Folder 271)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) Panel - Report, 1976 (Box 36, Folder 272)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) Panel - Report, 1976 (Box 37, Folder 273)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) Panel - Source Material, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 274)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) Panel - Source Material, 1973-1976 (Box 37, Folder 275)
    - American Council for the Arts in Education (ACAE) Panel - Source Material, n.d. (Box 37, Folder 276)
    - National Council for the Arts in Education (NCAIE) - Arts/Worth Program, 1958, 1964-1972 (Box 37, Folder 277)
    - National Council for the Arts in Education (NCAIE) - Conference Proceedings, 1962-1968 (Box 38, Folder 278)
    - National Council for the Arts in Education (NCAIE) - Conference Proceedings, 1962-1968 (Box 38, Folder 279)
    - National Council for the Arts in Education (NCAIE) - Conferences and Meetings, 1971-1972 (Box 38, Folder 280)
    - National Council for the Arts in Education (NCAIE) - Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 38, Folder 281)
  - Chronological Files, B
    - 1968-1969, 1971, 1968-1971 (Box 38, Folder 282)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 283)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 284)
    - 1972-1973 (Box 38, Folder 285)
    - January 1973 - August 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 286)
    - January 1973 - August 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 287)
    - January 1973 - August 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 288)
    - January 1973 - August 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 289)
    - January 1973 - August 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 290)
    - January 1973 - August 1974, 1973-1974 (Box 39, Folder 291)
    - September 1974 - June 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 292)
    - September 1974 - June 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 293)
    - September 1974 - June 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 294)
    - September 1974 - June 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 295)
    - September 1974 - June 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 296)
    - September 1974 - June 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 297)
    - September 1974 - June 1975, 1974-1975 (Box 40, Folder 298)
    - July 1975 - 1979 (Box 41, Folder 299)
    - July 1975 - 1979 (Box 41, Folder 300)
    - July 1975 - 1979 (Box 41, Folder 301)
    - July 1975 - 1979 (Box 41, Folder 302)
    - July 1975 - 1979 (Box 41, Folder 303)
- Financial Records, 1967-1978; 5; 2.2 Cubic Feet
  This series consists of audits, check stubs, correspondence, petty cash slips, receipts, and tax records.
  This series is arranged alphabetically by subject (e.g. tax records, loans, staff expenses) or by document type (e.g. audit, receipts).
  - Audits, 1976-1977 (Box 42, Folder 304)
  - Check Stubs - Chase Manhattan Account, August 1, 1975-August 8, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 305)
  - Check Stubs - Chase Manhattan Account, August 1, 1975-August 8, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 306)
  - Check Stubs - Citibank Account, October 29, 1974-June 13, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 307)
  - Check Stubs - Citibank Account, October 29, 1974-June 13, 1977 (Box 42, Folder 308)
  - Conferences, 1975-June 1976 (Box 42, Folder 309)
  - Conferences, 1975-June 1976 (Box 42, Folder 310)
  - Conference, October 1-3, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 311)
  - Conference, May 23-24, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 312)
  - Conferences - Panel Expenses, 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 313)
  - List of Incoming Checks, 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 314)
  - Returned (Box 43, Folder 315)
  - Payroll, 1975-1977 (Box 43, Folder 316)
  - Petty Cash Slips, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 317)
  - Petty Cash Slips, 1975-1976 (Box 43, Folder 318)
  - Petty Cash Slips, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 319)
  - Petty Cash Slips, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 320)
  - Petty Cash Slips, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 321)
  - Petty Cash Slips, 1977-1978 (Box 44, Folder 322)
  - Receipts (A), 1967-1969 (Box 44, Folder 323)
  - Receipts - ACA Publications, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 324)
  - Receipts - Ace Sound Rental Company, 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 325)
  - Receipts - Advisory Committee Meetings, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 326)
  - Receipts - American Building Maintenance, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 327)
  - Receipts - Amtrak, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 328)
  - Receipts - Apeco, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 329)
  - Receipts - Associated Messenger Service, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 330)
  - Receipts (B), 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 331)
  - Receipts - Berkey K&L Custom Services, n.d. (Box 44, Folder 332)
  - Receipts - Blue Cross/Blue Shield, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 333)
  - Receipts - Brook Street Bureau, 1976-1977 (Box 44, Folder 334)
  - Receipts (C), 1975-1976 (Box 44, Folder 335)
  - Receipts - Central Midwestern Regional Educational Laboratory (CEMREL), 1974 (Box 45, Folder 336)
  - Receipts (D), 1975-1976 (Box 45, Folder 337)
  - Receipts - Don Travel Service, 1975 (Box 45, Folder 338)
  - Receipts (E), n.d. (Box 45, Folder 339)
  - Receipts - Electra, 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 340)
  - Receipts (F-G), 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 341)
  - Receipts (F-G), 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 342)
  - Receipts - Gensup, 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 343)
  - Receipts - Guardian Food Service, 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 344)
  - Receipts (H), 1974-1976 (Box 45, Folder 345)
  - Receipts - International Business Machines (IBM), 1976-1977 (Box 45, Folder 346)
  - Receipts - Insurance, 1976 (Box 45, Folder 347)
  - Receipts (J-S), 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 348)
  - Receipts (J-S), 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 349)
  - Receipts (J-S), 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 350)
  - Receipts (J-S), 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 351)
  - Receipts (J-S), 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 352)
  - Receipts (J-S), 1975-1977 (Box 45, Folder 353)
  - Receipts - S&S Stationery Company, 1974-1975 (Box 45, Folder 354)
  - Receipts - S&S Stationery Company, 1976-1977 (Box 46, Folder 355)
  - Receipts - Spencer, Donald L., 1975-1978 (Box 46, Folder 356)
  - Receipts - Spencer, Dorothy, 1975-1978 (Box 46, Folder 357)
  - Receipts (T-Z), 1974-1977 (Box 46, Folder 358)
  - Receipts - Xerox, 1974-1977 (Box 46, Folder 359)
  - Research Expenses, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 360)
  - Staff Expenses, 1975-1976 (Box 46, Folder 361)
  - Staff Expenses - Howard, Margaret, 1974-1976 (Box 46, Folder 362)
  - Taxes - Federal, 1974-1978 (Box 46, Folder 363)
  - Taxes - Federal and New York State Unemployment Insurance, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 364)
  - Taxes - New York City, 1975-1977 (Box 47, Folder 365)
  - Taxes - New York State, 1975-1976 (Box 47, Folder 366)
  - Conference - Miscellaneous Arrangements, May 24, 1975 (Box 48, Folder 367)
  - Research Paper - Simmons, Joan H. - "State Education Policy", 1976 (Box 48, Folder 368)
  - Site Information Questionnaire - Compilation Files (Master Copy), 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 369)
  - Site Information Questionnaire - Summary of District Questionnaire (D. Polsky), 1975-1976 (Box 48, Folder 370)
  - Panel Report - Bills (Innovative Graphics International), 1978 (Box 48, Folder 371)
  - Panel Report - Mailing Lists, 1977 (Box 48, Folder 372)
  - Returned (Box 48, Folder 373)
- Arts, Education and Americans Panel photographs, 1041
  Arts, Education, and Americans Panel
  - Artists - Miscellany (Box 18, Folder 244)
  - Used in "Coming to Our Senses", 1977 (Box 18, Folder 245)
  - Considered for "Coming to Our Senses" - Not Used (Box 18, Folder 246)
  - Conference, September 29, 1977 - Columbus, Ohio (Box 19, Folder 247)
  - Portraits - Miscellany (Box 19, Folder 248)
  - Panel Meetings and Site Visits, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 249)
  - Panel Meetings and Site Visits, 1975-1977 - 2 (Box 19, Folder 250)
  - Panel Meetings and Site Visits, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 251)
  - Panel Meetings and Site Visits - Negatives, 1975-1977 (Box 19, Folder 252)
  - Negatives - Miscellany (Box 19, Folder 253)
  - Panel Meetings and Site Visits - Slides, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 254)
  - Panel Meetings and Site Visits - Slides, 1975-1977 (Box 20, Folder 255)